ebroadcast.com.au 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy

| 

**Privacy Policy**

|   
---|---  
  
eBroadcast is committed to your privacy and security. We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to others in ways different to those stated in this statement.

This Privacy Statement sets out:

  * what information we collect and how we collect it;
  * how we use that information;
  * who the information is provided to;
  * what procedures are in place to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and
  * how you can correct any inaccuracies of personal information collected by us.

We will not collect any personal information about you except when you knowingly provide it. Personal information is information that can identify you personally, for example your name or email address.

We will not reveal personal information we collect to third parties. 

**Cookies**

When you visit ebroadcast.com.au, we or our third party ad server may collect information about your visit using a feature called a "cookie". Also, if you have previously provided personal information to us, we may retain information about the frequency and contents of your visits to us. We use this information to aggregate information about the session length, number of visits to our site, the popularity of various areas of our site, and to deliver relevant advertisements to your browser.

**Alerts and Newsletters**

You can always change your preferences about alerts or emails you receive by visiting the site where you signed up and logging in. You may always unsubscribe from alerts and newsletters to which you have subscribed.

**Discussion Boards**

eBroadcast will never collect personal information from you when you use a chat room or discussion board. Such forums are considered public and you are responsible for personal information you choose to disclose in these areas. You should always be careful if distributing personal information in this matter. You are solely responsible for your interactions with other forum members. We reserve the right, but have no obligation, to monitor disputes between you and other members.

**Release**

You hereby acknowledge and agree that under no circumstances will eBroadcast Australia, its directors, its employees or any third party content provider to eBroadcast Australia be liable to you or any third party for any loss whatsoever caused by your reliance on information obtained through the site, as well any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages or injury arising out of the use or inability to use the service or out of breach of any warranty, or caused by any failure or computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorised access to and/or alteration of the eBroadcast Australia site.

In the event that you have any claim or action against any other member arising from that member's use of our Website or the Service, you agree to pursue such claim or action independently of and without any demands from us, and you release us from all claims, liability and damages, arising from or in any way connected to the claim or action.

In the event that a claim or action is brought against us from your activities or use of the Website or the Service, including any breach by you of this Agreement or any charges or complaints made by other parties against you, you agree to pay, hold harmless and defend us in the claim or action. You also agree to cooperate as fully as reasonably required in the defence of any claim and allow us to assume the exclusive defence and control of the matter.
